{
    "id": "9eb6fa0573b74c45bdce42d2a2945ee6",
    "title": "Tense Consistency Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "If the company followed the quality guidelines, they …………………… not land in trouble.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fbd2299da4784fda8b9af58e9e396c03"
        },
        {
            "question": "The telephone …………………. while I was having a bath.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rings",
                "rang",
                "is ringing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a7ee6ae0f2f546a7a20c18fe2d64a341"
        },
        {
            "question": "Since its conception in the early 1970s, the internet ………………… . in popularity.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "grew",
                "grow",
                "has grown"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9251f6c2b6f04535b98675ce4564839b"
        },
        {
            "question": "If she had acted more responsibly, everything ………………… all right.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would be",
                "would have been"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "13de051974414cdb8b4b15e69756ffe7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Thousands of people ……………………… see the art exhibition before it closes on Friday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "54d05d92f5dd459c8ddcf89d718788dc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Captain James Cook ………………… . by Hawaiian islanders in 1779 while he was on a visit to Alaska.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "killed",
                "had killed",
                "was killed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c4ceb9d6e6074556a6d4b92be937999d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was terribly disappointed with my marks because I …………………… really hard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "worked",
                "had worked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "617d4101697e4373bb280c9bb08b3202"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher started asking questions as soon as she ……………………… the lessons.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "finished",
                "has finished",
                "was finished"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6d0746a0be6641c894d8f0e755f90e88"
        },
        {
            "question": "Everyone …………………… that she would return safely.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hoped",
                "had hoped",
                "has hoped"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5eb5e6925f4e423fabed3cfcd3ddc8ba"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy confessed that he ………………… . the money.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has taken",
                "had taken"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e06a8067b98e4bfcb2b058f1e79de418"
        }
    ]
}